[
    {
        "front": "たちます ❘",
        "back": "stand up",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "すわります ❘",
        "back": "sit down",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "つかいます ❘",
        "back": "use",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "おきます ❘",
        "back": "put",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "つくります ❘",
        "back": "make, produce",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "うります ❘",
        "back": "sell",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "しります ❘",
        "back": "get to know",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "すみます ❘",
        "back": "to live",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅうします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "do research",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "しっています",
        "back": "know",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "すんでいます\n「おおさかに～」",
        "back": "live [in Osaka]",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "しりょう",
        "back": "materials, data",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "カタログ",
        "back": "catalog",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "じこくひょう",
        "back": "timetable",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "ふく",
        "back": "clothes",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "せいひん",
        "back": "products",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "ソフト",
        "back": "software",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "せんもん",
        "back": "speciality, field of study",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "はいしゃ",
        "back": "dentist",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "とこや",
        "back": "barber",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "プレイガイド",
        "back": "play (theater) guide",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "どくしん",
        "back": "single, unmarried",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "とくに",
        "back": "especially",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "おもいだします ❘",
        "back": "remember, recollect",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "ごかぞく",
        "back": "your family",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "いらっしゃいます ❘",
        "back": "be (honorific equivalent of います)",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "こうこう",
        "back": "senior high school",
        "chapter": 15
    },
    {
        "front": "おかし",
        "back": "sweets",
        "chapter": 15
    }
]